http://www.huddlehouse.com/privacy/

We’re committed to the safety and well-being of our community and employees. As we continue to learn more about COVID-19 and work with local partners, your restaurant may be impacted by a closure or changing hours. Please call ahead to confirm. For more information, click on this link.Privacy PolicyIntroduction:
Huddle House, Inc. (Huddle House) understands the importance of protecting the privacy of its website users.  For that reason, Huddle House has adopted this privacy policy (this “Policy”) in order to inform you of its policies regarding personal information Huddle House collects about you through our engagement with you and through our services, programs and products, including, our website www.huddlehouse.com (the “Website”), the Huddle House mobile app (the “Mobile App”). This Privacy Policy describes the policies and practices of Huddle House regarding collection of information from visitors to its websites and social media pages and the uses, maintenance, protection and disclosure of such information by Huddle House.  This website is intended for United States residents only; if you are visiting this website from a location outside the United States, your communications through this website will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international borders, and, in so doing, you consent to the processing or collection of your information in the United States.
This Privacy Policy also applies to the practices of Huddle House’s wholly owned subsidiaries, except that if such a subsidiary publishes its own privacy policy, that policy will instead apply to the practices of that subsidiary.
It does not apply to information collected by us offline or through other means or by any third party.
Please read this policy carefully to understand our practices and policies regarding your information and how we will treat it.
If you do not agree with our policies or procedures, you have the option not to use this website.
By accessing, using or interacting with this website, you agree to this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time (see the section entitled “Changes to Our Privacy Policy” below).
Your continued use of this website after we make changes to this Privacy Policy is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. Personal Information Huddle House Collects:  Certain areas of Huddle House’s website and mobile app may require individuals to register and/or create an account to enable access to content, services and offers.  Information that individuals opt to provide to Huddle House in connection with registration may include name, date of birth, gender, home address or ZIP code, e-mail address, phone number and preferred Huddle House location.   Huddle House collects such information as part of the registration process.  Huddle House may also use a variety of technologies to collect information directly from individuals, including cookies and web beacons, and may collect information provided by the individual’s web browser, such as internet protocol address and operating system.  Our web server uses an extended log file format which captures: date and time of visit, referring address (location from which a visitor comes to this website), types of computing devices and Internet browsers, and visitors’ IP addresses. (Each computer that connects to the Internet is assigned a unique number, an IP address, for identification purposes). The log file does not capture a visitor’s email address. In some instances, Huddle House may also collect information from third parties, upon whom we rely to provide services. We use both business partners and service providers, such as payment processors and analytics providers, to perform services on our behalf. Some of these partners may have access to information about you that we may or may not otherwise have and may share some or all of this information with us. We may use this information to administer and improve Our Website and Services to deliver better and more personalized marketing and advertising campaigns, including: Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.Speed up your searches.Recognize you when you return to our Website.In addition to the categories of information referenced above, Huddle House may also collect aggregated data or anonymized data that does not directly identify you.Huddle House Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information with Others:  Most of the information collected by Huddle House is statistical data that is not capable of identifying a particular individual (Anonymous Data).  However, the information collected by Huddle House may include information that may allow an individual to be personally identified (PII).  If an individual does not wish for Huddle House to share information with others as described in this Privacy Policy, such individual may choose not to interact with Huddle House’s website or social media pages.  In all instances, Huddle House endeavors to design and implement its practices and policies to abide by applicable law and to reasonably secure and protect information we collect from individuals against unauthorized disclosure and third-party access.  In some cases, Huddle House may disclose PII to third parties, such as:Our service providers: We contract with companies who help with parts of our business operations. We require that our service providers only use PII in connection with the services they perform for us, including services performed in fulfilling the purpose for which an individual provided PII.Service providers to our advertisers: Our advertisers may contract with companies who handle data (such as advertisers’ customer lists) for them.Our subsidiaries and related companies:  Our affiliates may assist Huddle House in providing and marketing its services to the public, including through the use and analysis of information we collect from individuals.Courts or opposing parties in legal proceedings: When we are under a legal obligation to do so, for example to comply with a binding order of a court, or where disclosure is necessary to exercise, establish or defend the legal rights of Huddle House, our advertisers or any other third party.An acquirer or merger partner in connection with a sale of our business: If a third party acquires some or all of our business or assets or is merged with Huddle House, we may disclose PII in connection with the sale.The consuming public in connection with individuals’ feedback provided to Huddle House:  If an individual provides feedback or commentary to us, we may use and disclose such feedback and commentary for any purpose, provided that if we store that feedback in a manner that connects it to the individual and his or her PII, we will treat that PII in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Third Parties Using Aggregated and/or Anonymized Information:
We may disclose aggregated, anonymized information to our advertisers and other third parties.Any third party in accordance individuals’ express permission.We also share anonymized technical data that we collect about individuals’ Internet connections, browsing habits and computing devices and web browsers (such as data relating to our cookies, tracking pixels and similar technologies) with other advertising companies in the digital advertising ecosystem. This enables them and us to better target ads to individuals. In all instances of disclosure of individual information, including PII, to third parties, Huddle House endeavors to require such third parties to abide by privacy policies and practices that are consistent with those discussed in this Privacy Policy, but Huddle House is not responsible for the privacy practices of those third parties.  Huddle House encourages individuals to review the applicable privacy policies of all third parties to which they may be directed in connection with Huddle House’s website and social media pages.Data Security:  Huddle House has implemented measures designed to secure personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. Examples of our safeguards include firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls, and administrative information controls. The safety and security of personal information also depends on individual conduct – where Huddle House has given individuals access to certain parts of its website or social media pages through passwords and the like, such individuals are responsible for keeping such access information confidential.  Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not fully secure, and although Huddle House endeavors to protect personal information against unauthorized access or distribution, we cannot guarantee the security of personal information transmitted to Huddle House’s website or social media pages, and such transmission of personal information is at the individual’s own risk. As a result, we recommend that you help us keep your information safe by taking reasonable steps such as keeping your passwords private, and not disclosing personal data in places that can be accessed publicly. Data Retention: We retain your information only for as long as is necessary to provide the Services and to fulfill the transactions you have requested, or for other necessary purposes such as complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements.Removal of Cookies from Computing Devices: Individuals may remove cookies their computing devices’ memories, including cookies placed by or through the use of the Huddle House website or social media pages. Please check with the applicable browser provider for more information on removing cookies.Nature of Huddle House’s Use of Information Collected:  The information collected by Huddle House on its websites and through its social media pages is used to improve the services we offer, to improve the website and social media content we provide, to contact customers regarding updates to such content and for other marketing purposes, including targeted marketing of offers related to our Huddle Club, Huddle Up Rewards or other marketing programs.Links to Other Sites: In some areas of the Website or the Mobile App, we may provide a link to another website. Other websites, including social media sites, have their own policies regarding privacy and security, and these may vary from ours.Opting Out of Receiving Further Huddle House Communication:  We recognize how important online privacy is, so we offer the following options for controlling the targeted ads individuals receive and how we use collected data (California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices – please see the “California Privacy Rights” section below):Individuals can opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by Huddle House: Individuals can opt out of receiving targeted ads served by Huddle House or on its behalf by clicking on the opt-out icon in the ads Huddle House serves. Please note that, if an individual deletes cookies or upgrades a web browser after having opted out, additional opt-out action may be required. Further, if an individual uses multiple browsers or devices, opt-out action may be required on each browser or device.Individuals can opt-out of receiving targeted, interest-based or on-line behavioral ads through advertising associations: Individuals may use the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) opt-out tool at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/, which will allow the individuals to opt out of seeing targeted ads from Huddle House and from NAI-approved member companies.  Individuals may also opt out of receiving targeted, interest-based or on-line behavioral ads from other companies that perform ad targeting services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance website at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ and Your Online Choices website at http://www.youronlinechoices.com/.Access to and correction of PII held by Huddle House:  If an individual wishes to gain access to, correct, amend or delete any PII or other information about such individual held by Huddle House, he or she may submit a request to Huddle House’s privacy officer at the address provided below.  Huddle House will exercise good faith efforts to provide access to such information to the extent it is available within a reasonable time, and to correct, amend or delete such information to the extent it is believed to be inaccurate or sought to be deleted, except where the burden or expense of providing access, correction or amendment would be disproportionate to the risks to the privacy of the individual in the particular instance or where the rights of other persons would be violated.Children’s Privacy: This website is not intended for children under 13 years of age.
No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on this website.
Huddle House does not knowingly collect personal information from children – Huddle House websites and loyalty programs are not designed to attract, nor do they seek to provide services to, any persons under the age of 13 years.  Users under the age of 13 must not use or provide any information on this website or on or through any of its features, and must not register on this website or make any purchase through this website or use any of its interactive features to provide any information about themselves to us, including name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or any screen name or user name in use.
If we learn that an individual interacting with Huddle House’s website or social media pages is under the age of 13 years, we will delete that information from our databases.
If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact our Privacy Officer at Privacy@HuddleHouse.com.California Privacy Rights:
If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information.
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our website who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of PII to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes.
To make such a request, please send an e-mail request to our Privacy Officer at Privacy@HuddleHouse.com, with the subject line “California Privacy Rights”.
Pursuant to applicable California law, including the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Huddle House makes the following disclosures regarding the person information Huddle House has collected within the last 12 months:Category of Personal InformationCategory of Source from Which Data is CollectedPurpose of CollectionFirst and last name, postal address and/or zip code, email address, phone number, date of birth, gender, military or veteran statusDirectly from the user/customerMarketing (including advertising, customer acquisition and lead generation, performance media, audience segmentation, event organization, web traffic analytics, brand promotion and analytics, surveys and consumer research, campaigns, management of influencer and other partner relationships, social media content distribution and analytics, mobile application communications, contest administration, and customer engagement and analytics)Operational purposes (including order processing, payment, gift card, voucher and coupon processing, receipt processing, anti-fraud, sales data reporting, provision of food truck services, third-party delivery coordination, and mobile application and kiosk services and analytics)Development and real estate for the purpose of expanding the ServicesCustomer ServiceMobile application log-in credentialsDirectly from the user/customerTo enable user access to our mobile applicationsExternal social network credentialsDirectly from the user/customerTo enable users to link their social network accounts with our mobile applicationsCredit card or other payment informationDirectly from the user/customerMarketing (including surveys and consumer research, and management of influencer and other partner relationships)Operational purposes (including order processing, payment, gift card, voucher and coupon processing, receipt processing, anti-fraud, sales data reporting, and mobile application and kiosk services and analytics)Location dataCookiesTo provide users with location-specific services, such as showing nearby restaurants in our mobile applicationDining preferences, who you typically dine with, when you normally visit our restaurant locations, how often you visit our restaurant locationsDirectly from the user/customerTo market our services to you and tailor offers to your interestsDemographic informationDirectly from the user/customerTo market our services to you and tailor offers to your interestsMetadata about how users access and use our Sites and mobile applicationsCookies, web beacons, pixels, social media widgets, and other tracking technologiesMarketing (including advertising, customer acquisition and lead generation, performance media, audience segmentation, event organization, web traffic analytics, brand promotion and analytics, surveys and consumer research, campaigns, management of influencer and other partner relationships, social media content distribution and analytics, mobile application communications, contest administration, and customer engagement and analytics)To conduct data analytics In accordance with the CCPA, California residents to request that we disclose the following information about our collection and use of “Personal Information,” over the past twelve months: The categories of Personal Information we collect about you.The categories of sources for the Personal Information we collect about you.Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that Personal Information.The specific pieces of Personal Information collected about you.If we disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose, a list of the categories of Personal Information we have disclosed in the prior twelve months.If we sold your Personal Information for a business purpose, a list of the categories of Personal Information we have sold in the prior twelve months.Deletion of your personal informationAn opt out of having your personal information disclosed or sold to third parties To ask for a record of the information we hold about you, or to ask us to delete your information please visit https://www.huddlehouse.com/privacy-request, email privacy@huddlehouse.com or call us at 770-325-1300. You must provide enough information that we can very who you are and that you are a resident of the State of California. If you have an account with us, we will also verify your identity through our existing authentication practices for your account.Notice to California Residents Under the Age of 18:
If you are under the age of 18, and we have actual knowledge of your age, under California law you may request and obtain removal of certain content or information you have provided to us. To do so, please contact our Privacy Officer at Privacy@HuddleHouse.com. Please be aware that removal of your information does not ensure complete removal of the content. For example, removal may not be permitted if another provision of law requires the content to be maintained.Non-United States Persons:
Huddle House does not operate restaurants or other facilities outside the United States.
This website is hosted in the United States and is not intended for non-United States persons.
Huddle House processes data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and with applicable law in the United States.
Any personal information about non-United States persons (including persons resident in the European Union (“EU”) and considered EU data subjects) provided via this website is processed in the United States by Huddle House or by a third party acting on behalf of Huddle House.
In certain countries outside the United States, individuals are entitled to the right to access, correct, transmit, restrict, delete and object to processing of the personal information we have collected, and may also be entitled to withdraw consent to processing of personal information.
When you provide personal information to Huddle House through this website, you consent to the processing of your information in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
If you are an EU data subject, at any time you wish to know what data we process about you, you can request to gain access to that information by making a request of privacy@huddlehouse.com, and Huddle House will provide you with reasonable opportunities to gain access to and update or delete your information.
If you are an EU data subject, you have certain other rights with respect to your information provided to Huddle House – you can make any requests with respect to those rights by e-mail to our Privacy Officer at Privacy@HuddleHouse.com.Changes to Our Privacy Policy:
Huddle House’s policy is to post any changes to this Privacy Policy on this page and to provide notice of any material changes made to how we treat users’ personal information through notice posted on the Huddle House website’s homepage.  We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check back frequently for any such changes.
It is the user’s responsibility to periodically visit this page to check for any changes to this Privacy Policy.
Any use of this website constitutes the applicable individual’s agreement to this Privacy Policy as in effect on the date of such use.
The date this Privacy Policy was last updated is identified below.Contact information:  To ask questions, comment about this Privacy Policy or Huddle House’s privacy practices, or to request access, changes or amendments to the personal information Huddle House stores about an individual, please use the following contact information:Huddle House Privacy OfficerEmail: Privacy@HuddleHouse.comPhone: 770-325-1300Address: 5901-B Peachtree Dunwoody Road, NESTE 450Sandy Springs, GA 30328Last Updated: January 2, 2020Looks like we need to find you a storeSearch for locations near you.Use your locationorSearch
